peoplelogic.com.au 2017-02-19

# WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

This website is owned and operated by Swift Digital. By using this site, you agree to the Internet Privacy Policy of this website.

The website Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through the use of this website.

All personal Information collected by Swift Digital is protected by [Privacy Act 1988](http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/privacy-act/the-privacy-act). We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our website, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual such as: email address and contact numbers.

This Website Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the website, will be dealt with. This Internet Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome your comments and feedback at [privacy@swiftdigital.com.au](mailto:privacy@swiftdigital.com.au) or by mail to Swift Digital’s Sydney office: Privacy officer, 31-33 Trafalgar Street, Enmore, NSW 2042, Australia.

##### Personal Information

  1. Personal information about visitors to our site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted by you. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia. 

We collect your information when:  
You subscribe to our newsletters  
You make an enquiry using our web forms  
You contribute to our forums or blogs

##### Use of Information

  2. Personal information that visitors submit to our site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted. 

We will send you information you subscribed for.  
We will contact you using your information regarding any enquiries.   
We will provide updates of our services.

##### Disclosure

  3. Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information will not be shared or sold to third parties. We may however disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.

##### Security

  4. We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure.
  5. However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
  6. In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.

##### Collecting Information from Users

  7. _IP Addresses_  
Our web servers gather your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or support issues with our services. Again, information is gathered in aggregate only and cannot be traced to an individual user.
  8. _Cookies and Applets_  
We use cookies to provide you with a better experience. These cookies allow us to increase your security by storing your session ID and are a way of monitoring single user access. This aggregate, non-personal information is collated and provided to us to assist in analysing the usage of the site. 

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie so that you will have an opportunity to either accept or reject it in each instance. However you should note that refusing cookies may have negative impact on the usability of the website.

##### Access to Information

  9. We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you may contact us to have the information corrected. By contacting us through [privacy@swiftdigital.com.au](mailto:privacy@swiftdigital.com.au) or by mailing to our postal address: Privacy Officer, 31-33 Trafalgar Street, Enmore, NSW 2042, Australia.
  10. In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.

##### Problems or questions

  11. If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our websites, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@swiftdigital.com.au](mailto:privacy@swiftdigital.com.au) or by mailing to our postal address: Privacy officer, 31-33 Trafalgar Street, Enmore, NSW 2042, Australia. 

All complaints will be responded to within 10 business days. We will investigate and attempt to resolve your query or complaint within 30 business days or such longer period as is necessary and notified to you by our Privacy Officer.

  12. For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website: <http://www.privacy.gov.au/>.
